Something happened 30 years ago...
Fed Up is a documentary film directed by Stephanie Soechtig.
Fed Up blows the lid off everything we thought we knew about food and weight loss,
revealing a 30-year campaign by the food industry, aided by the U.S.
government, to mislead and confuse the American public, resulting
in one of the largest health epidemics in history.
Narrator, played by Katie Couric.
Self, played by Michael Pollan.
Self, played by Bill Clinton.
Self, played by Tom Vilsack.
Self, played by Kelly Brownell.
Self, played by Michael Bloomberg.
Fed Up is a 2014 American documentary film directed,
written and produced by Stephanie Soechtig.
The film focuses on the causes of obesity in the US, presenting evidence showing large quantities of sugar in processed foods are an overlooked root
of the problem, and points to the monied lobbying power of "Big Sugar" in blocking attempts to enact policies to address the issue.
The film explores themes of junk food, obesity, food
industry, public health, weight loss.